

ABOUT ME

O Who am I

I'm Cristian, a 22-year-old student at KTH. I enjoy exploring new things, testing new technologies and improving my knowledge in the world of computer science

O My goals

To work in a role where I can bridge the gap between machine learning and software development in order to make better products

WORK EXPERIENCE

O WeKnowIT - App developer

Mars 2018- present

Developing customized apps with React Native for customers. Resposible for planning, building and delivering the entire product

O Topgolf Sweden - Software developer

May 2017 - August 2017

Built a Windows application from scratch with C# and WPF

EDUCATION

KTH - Royal Institute of Technology

August 2015 - present

Pursuing a M.Sc in Computer Science with a specialization in data science and machine learning

O Åva Upper Secondary School

August 2012 - June 2015

Technology program

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

O Project leader

January 2018 - December 2018

Head of the reception of new students at the computer science chapter. Lead a team of 60 students to organize 5 weeks of events for 200 people to partake in

Group leader

January 2017 - December 2017

Lead a group of 26 students that worked with the reception of new students at the computer science chapter

SKILLS

Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, React Native, Redux, Node, C#, WPF, Java, Python, $^{\rm O}$ Git. SOL